anyflip.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy | AnyFlip

### Privacy Policy

The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to provide the Service to you. We will use your email address, without further consent, for customer service purposes, or to contact you regarding your account or payment info with using the service.

The service does not share your personally identifiable information, including any of your user profile data that you create, with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on the Service becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction. Slide Html5 may share personally identifiable information about our users with third parties, including: 

a. with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; 

b. when we have a good faith belief it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; 

c. where required by law; 

d. at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights or property of the Service or any third party. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated companies, sub-contractors, other agents or businesses or persons to: provide ebook hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Slide Html5 in improving the Service and creating new service features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures to keep your information secure. Slide Html5 may also disclose to third parties anonymous aggregated user information that is not personally identifiable.
